Dental School Short Run Publications UP108
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Dental School Short Run Publications
1915 -- 2005
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Dental Medicine
UP108
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains multiple short- run publications of the Tufts University School of Dental Medicine from 1915 to 2005 of which only a small number ever appeared.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts University School of Dental Medicine was established in 1868 as Boston Dental College. It was incorporated into Tufts College in 1899. Although founded as a school to educate students from New England, today Tufts is renowned throughout the United States and the world as a center for academic and clinical excellence. Tufts boasts over 6,900 alumni composed of individuals from all fifty states and thirty-nine countries. The majority of the alumni outside of the USA have completed an Advanced Education Certificate program. Students receive a comprehensive education emphasizing the importance of didactic coursework, clinical experience, and practice management that prepares them to enter the work force as confident, proficient clinicians.
- Dental School Short Run Publications, 1915 -- 2005; UP108.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains multiple short- run publications of the Tufts University School of Dental Medicine from 1915 to 2005 of which only a small number ever appeared.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged as publications are found and chronologically within each publication.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Doings, 1915; UP108.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association Annual Meeting, 1917 -- 1988; UP108.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, Dental School Student Council, 1940 -- 1950; UP108.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Administrative and Academic Calendar, 1975 -- 1977; UP108.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - News and Comments from the Dean, 1969 -- 1976; UP108.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Newsletter, 1963 -- 1964; UP108.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Dental Medicine Newsletter, 1969 -- 1970; UP108.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - News and Comments Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1977 -- 1980; UP108.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - News and Comments Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1981 -- 1984; UP108.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - News and Comments Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1985-05 -- 1987-01; UP108.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - The Dental Mirror, Winter, 2005; UP108.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - News @ Tufts Dental, 2003-07-02; UP108.001.001.00012 (Box 1)